GIORDANNA DE GREGORIIS

AVENIDA VISCONDE DE SOUZA FRANCO, 601 - APT 1901 | BELÉM, PA 66053-000

+55 (91) 98898-6521 | contato@gior.me | gior.grs@gmail.com

- gior.me
- linkedin.com/in/gregoriis
- github.com/giordanna

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a Full-Stack Web Developer, graduated in Computer Science from the Federal University of Pará, and I am passionate about education. I worked in institutions of distance education, which enabled me to realize that technologies can and should be allied with education. I developed projects with python, PHP, MySQL, Angular and React.js.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Angular 7 (formerly Angular 2) The Complete Guide: ude.my/UC-IJJVE81Q
- Full-Stack Web Developer: confirm.udacity.com/CCLAJDSA

PARTICIPATIONS

- DevOpsDays Belém 2018;
- Seminar "Contribuindo com Software Livre: O Programa Google Summer of Code";
- Arduino Day Belém 2015.

EXPERIENCE

FEDERAL UNIVERSITY OF PARÁ

Editorial Assistant | Belém, PA | January 2018 – June 2018

- Developed web platforms;
- Diagramed e-books;
- Produced graphic art.
- Work done at the Center for Innovation and Applied Technologies for Teaching and Extension (NITAE²), located at the Federal University of Pará (UFPA), through the Support Foundation and Research Development (Fadesp).

Service Industry | Belém, PA | August 2017 – January 2018

- Developed web platforms;
- Diagramed e-books;
- Produced graphic art.
- Work done at the Distance Education Advisory (AEDI), located at the Federal University of Pará (UFPA).

Internship | Belém, PA | February 2014 - December 2015

- Diagramed e-books;
- Produced graphic art.
- Work done at the Distance Education Advisory (AEDI), located at the Federal University of Pará (UFPA), with the help of a grant from the Pro-Rectorate of Administration (PROAD).

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S DEGREE in Computer Science | Coeficiente de Rendimento Geral (CRG): 7.9762 Federal University of Pará